A Guide to the Katherine Gentry Bushman Papers, 1961-1997
Library of Virginia
- Family Research Files (Box 1-87a)
  - Liptrap-Gabbert (Box 51, Folder 8-9)
  - Livick (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Lockhart (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Logan (Box 51, Folder 12-13)
  - Long (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Lockridge-Ptomey-Daggy (Box 52, Folder 2-3)
  - Long-Burkett (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Long-Burkett-Sheets (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Looney (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Loop-Wilson (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Love (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Lowman, John (Box 52, Folder 9-10)
  - Lowman, William (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Lucas (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Lyman-H. D. Peck (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - "M" - Misc. (Box 53, Folder 1-5)
  - Mabrey (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Madison-Herring (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Magee-Long (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Magill (Box 53, Folder 9-10)
  - Malcolm (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Mann (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Mann-McClintock (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Marshall (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Marshall-Caldwell (Box 54, Folder 2-3)
  - Marshall-Gilkeson-Rutledge (Box 54, Folder 4-5)
  - Martin (Box 54, Folder 6-8)
  - Matheny (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Mathews (Box 54, Folder 10-11)
  - Mathews,William (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Mattinearly-Yost (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Maxwell (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Mayfield-Sullivan (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Mayo, Frederick (Box 55, Folder 2-3)
  - Mayo-Smith-Barrett;Pitman-Altrith-Cyford (Box 55, Folder 4-5)
  - Merritt, William (also Fitzpatrick) (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Messersmith-Hottel-Wagner (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Michael-Shutz-Huffer-Shaffer (Box 55, Folder 8-10)
  - Michael, William (of Rockingham Co.) (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Miller (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Miller, Abraham (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Daniel (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Miller, Henry (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Martin (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Miller-Bright-Collins (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Millsap (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Mitchell (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Moffett, John (Box 56, Folder 9-10)
  - Moffett-McDowell (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Mohler-Garber (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Mohler-Reeves-Fisher-Rogers (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Moneymaker-Swink (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
  - Monroe (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Moody (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Moore (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Moore, James (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Morloch (Box 57, Folder 7-8)
  - Morris (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Mose-Foley-Funk (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Moses-Underwood-Koontz (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Mowry, Henry (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Moyers-Myers (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Myers-Moyers (also Weeler-Wine-Layman-Reed-Smith-Bish) (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Myers, Michael (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - "Mc" - Misc. (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
  - McAleer (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - McCalley (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - McChesney (Box 58, Folder 6-7)
  - McClanahan (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - McClenachan (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - McClenachan-Madison (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - McClung (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - McClure (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - McComb-Macomb (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - McCorkle (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - McCormick (Box 59, Folder 2-4)
  - McCormick-Hall-McChesney (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - McCown (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - McCoy-Taylor (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - McCray (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - McCroskey-Poage (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - McCulloch-Harms (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - McCune (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - McCutchan (Box 59, Folder 12-18)
  - McCutchan, James (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - McCutchen-Fulton (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - McDonald (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - McDowell (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - McFall (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - McFarland (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - McGee-Thomson-Thompson-Brinley (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - McGlamery/McGlamory (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - McGuffin (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - McHenry (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - McIntosh (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - McKee (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - McKemy (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - McKinney (Box 60, Folder 14-16)
  - McMahon (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - McMurtry (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - McNair (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - McNeill (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - McNutt (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - McPheeters-Wardlaw (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - "N" - Misc. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Naher-Nair (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Newman-Humphries (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Nickell-Nichol (Box 61, Folder 10-11)
  - Nutty (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - "O" - Misc. (Box 61, Folder 13-14)
  - Friel-Friel (Box 61, Folder 15-16)
  - Olinger-Ellinger (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Ott (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Overall (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Owens (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - "P" - Misc. (Box 62, Folder 5-8)
  - Palmer, Larry (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Palmer (Peggy Joyner) (Box 62, Folder 10-11)
  - Parris-Hutchens (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Partin-Byrd-Hutchings (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Pates-Booth (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Patrick (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Patterson-Christian (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Patterson-Culton-Walker (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Patterson (Staunton) (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Patterson-McClung-Dever-Craig (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Patton, John (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Patton-Preston-Thompson-Floyd-Buchanan (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Paul-Hillis-Frazer (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Pauli-Pauly (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Paxton (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Peatt-Piatt-Pyatt-Donahoe (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Peck-Fenton-Fackler (Box 63, Folder 8-9)
  - Peebles (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Peery (Box 63, Folder 11-13)
  - Percy (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Perry-Riddle-Gilmore (Box 64, Folder 2-3)
  - Phillips (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Phillips, James (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Pickering-Biby (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Pierce (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Poage (Box 64, Folder 8-9)
  - Poff (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Points (Box 64, Folder 11-12)
  - Polk (Box 65, Folder 1-5)
  - Polk-Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 6-8)
  - Porter (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Powell (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Powers (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Price, Gen. Thomas Lawson (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Price-Halderman (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Props-Orebaugh (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Pullins-Usher (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Quisenberry (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - "R" - Misc. (Box 66, Folder 4-8)
  - Rader-Painter (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Ralston-Rutledge (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Rambo (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Ramsey (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Randolph-Frazier (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Rankin (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
  - Rankin-Curry-Sheets (Box 67, Folder 5-7)
  - Ransbottom-Crisman (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Rawley (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Rayburn (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Reed (Box 67, Folder 11-12)
  - Reed (Walker's Creek Area) (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Reed, Saunders (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Reese (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Reeves-Miller (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Reynolds (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Rhodes-Rodes-Roads (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Rhodes-Trayer-Knowles (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Riddle-Gilmore-Miller (Box 68, Folder 4-5)
  - Rider-Curry (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Rinehart (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Rippeto (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Risk (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Robertson (Box 68, Folder 10-11)
  - Robertson (Albemarle and Amherst) (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Robertson-Campbell-White (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Robertson-Crockett (Box 68, Folder 14-15)
  - Robertson-Harnsberger (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Robertson-Long Meadow Run (Box 69, Folder 2-3)
  - Robertson-Miscellaneous (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Robertson-Robinson (Box 69, Folder 5-6)
  - Robinson (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Rodes-Peters (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Rogers-Fisher (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Roland (Box 69, Folder 10-11)
  - Rosenberger-Zirkle-Kagey (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Ross (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Ross, William (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Rothgeb-Roadcap (Box 69, Folder 15-16)
  - Rowe (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Ruddell-Sharp-Custer (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Ruff (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Rusmisel (Box 70, Folder 4-5)
  - Russell (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Andrew Russell I (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Russell, John (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Rutherford (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Rutledge (Box 70, Folder 10-11)
  - "S" - Misc. (Box 70, Folder 12-14)
  - "S" - Misc. (cont.) (Box 71, Folder 1-3)
  - Salvage-Kring (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Sawyers (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Schindler-Zahn (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Schmid (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Scott (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Scott, Samuel (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Scrogham-Hawkins-Zerkle (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Seawright-Beard-Sproul (Box 71, Folder 11-12)
  - Seldomridge-Thomas (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Sellers (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Sensebach (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Shaffer-Shaver (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Shaner-Harner (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Shanklin-Garten (Box 72, Folder 1-3)
  - Sheets (Box 72, Folder 4-7)
  - Sheets, Abraham (son of John) (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Sheets, George (Pendleton Co.) and Henry (Shenandoah Co.) (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Sheets-Deavers-Spitzer-Pickering (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Sheets-Lindamood (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Shelly (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Shelton (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Sherman-Jones-Koogler-Gilmore (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Shields (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Shiplett (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Shoemaker (Box 72, Folder 17-18)
  - Shirley (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Shott (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Shreckhise (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Shuff (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Shuff-Keller (Box 73, Folder 5-6)
  - Shull-Good-Shafer (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Shultz (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Shultz-Wilson (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Shumate (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Sieg (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Silling (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Silor-Siler-Seiler (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Simmons (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Simond-Simonds (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Simms (Sims-Symes) (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Sipe (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Sites, John Sr. (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Slagle-Coiner (Box 73, Folder 19-20)
  - Slover (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Slusher (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Smallwood (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Smith (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Smith, R.R. (Jake) (also Neff) (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Smith-Houff-Quick-Hussey (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Smith-Rees-Bowen-Hildreth (Box 74, Folder 6-7)
  - Sniteman-Flory (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Snodgrass (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Snyder (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Son (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Spitler-Davis-Emmery (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - St. Clair (Sinclair) (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Stanton-Martin (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Staubus-Michael (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Steele (Box 75, Folder 1-4)
  - Stephenson-Huston (Houston) (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Stephenson-Wooddell (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Sterrett-Tate (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Stevenson-Stephenson (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Stover (Box 75, Folder 9-11)
  - Stover, Rev. Michael (incl. Grove, Gochenour, Miller, Sanger, Kindig) (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Strain (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Stuart (Box 76, Folder 1-5)
  - Sullivan-Murray (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Summers (Box 76, Folder 7-8)
  - Surface (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Sutler (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Swadley (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Swats (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Switzer (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - "T" - Misc. (Box 77, Folder 1-3)
  - Tally (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Tate (Box 77, Folder 5-8)
  - Tate, David (Botetourt) (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Taurman (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Taylor (Box 77, Folder 11-13)
  - Taylor-Gibson-Mosby-McCullough (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Teaford (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Teas (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Thacker-Whitesell-Davis-Mayo (Box 78, Folder 4-6)
  - Thomas (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Thomason-Apple (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Thompson (Box 78, Folder 9-10)
  - Thompson-Leeper (Box 78, Folder 11-12)
  - Thompson-Long (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Thompson-Stover (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Thomson-Hoge (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Thornton (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Thornton, Coats (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Todd (Box 79, Folder 4-5)
  - Todd-Henderson (Box 79, Folder 6-7)
  - Todd-Henderson-Lobban-Clarke (Box 79, Folder 8-10)
  - Turnispeed (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Tool-Haybarger-Fudge (Box 79, Folder 12-13)
  - Trigg-Ingles-Smith (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Trotter (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Trout (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Turk-Robertson (Box 80, Folder 5-8)
  - Turley (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Unroe (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - "V" - Misc. (Box 80, Folder 11-12)
  - Van Lear (Box 80, Folder 13-14)
  - Van Meter (Box 81, Folder 1-2)
  - Van Trump (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Vance (Box 81, Folder 4-5)
  - Vickers (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Vines/Vines-Hight (Box 81, Folder 7-8)
  - Vineyard-Tallett (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - "V-W" - Misc. (Box 81, Folder 10-12)
  - Waddell (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Wade-McFadden (Box 81, Folder 14-15)
  - Wade-Slaven-Ruckman (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Wagner-Padgett (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Walker (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Walker-Robson-Miller (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Walker-Rutherford (Box 82, Folder 5-6)
  - Wallace (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Walton (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Wanless (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Ward (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Warwick-Dunlap-Sitlington (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Washington (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Wear-Weir (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Weast (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Weaver (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Webb (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Wehrly (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Weikel (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Weller-Bish (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Wentz, Dr. Byron E. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - West (Box 83, Folder 6-8)
  - Westfall-Reese (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Whitlock (Box 83, Folder 10-11)
  - Whitman-Carlock (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Whitmore-Whitmer (Box 83, Folder 13-14)
  - Wiley (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Wilkerson (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Williams-Danner (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Willson, Col. John (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Willson-Larew (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Willson/Wilson (Box 84, Folder 5-7)
  - Wilmoth (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Wilson (Box 84, Folder 9-12)
  - Wilson-Doe Hill and Pendleton (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Wilson, Jim (Grandville, Mi.) (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Wilson, Maj. Thomas and John Wilson-Susannah (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Wilson-Misc. (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Col. John Wilson-Burgess (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Colonel John Wilson Families (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, John (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Wilson, Joshua (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Thomas Wilson (Waynesboro) (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Wilson, Woodrow (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Wilson-Reeves (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Windle-Young-Glass-Jamison-Glenn (Box 85, Folder 12-13)
  - Wine-Wynes-Wyant (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Winegar-Huffman (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Winkler-Woods (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Wiseman (Box 86, Folder 2-3)
  - Womeldorf (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Wood (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Woodley-Seahorn (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Woods (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Woods, Permenas (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Woodward (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Woolwine-Hammaker (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Wright (Box 86, Folder 11-12)
  - Wyat-Wyatt and Haute-Hawte Families in England and Virginia (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Wyatt (Mrs. Tinsley) (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Xaupi (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Yancey (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Yazel/Yeasell (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Yeager (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Yearout (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Yoakum (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Yost (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Youell (Box 87, Folder 2-3)
  - Young, George (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Young-Wise (Box 87, Folder 5-7)
  - "Z" - Misc. (Box 87, Folder 8-9)
  - Zimmerman (Box 87, Folder 10-12)
  - Zink (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Surname Card Index to Family Research Files (Box 87a)
- Subject Files (Box-folder Box 88 - Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Administrators Bond Book II, Augusta County, Virginia, 26 February 1812-23 September 1816 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Aronhime-Correspondence (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Augusta County, Virginia Court of Claims, 1782-1784 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Augusta County Historical Advisory Committee (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Augusta County Historical Society (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Augusta Co. Militia Roster Book (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Augusta Declaration (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Augusta German Project (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Augusta Historical Bulletin (Box 88, Folder 9-10)
  - Beverley Manor (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Black Records of Augusta County, Virginia (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - City Directory, 1899 (Augusta County and Staunton) (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - History of Clay County, Mo.-Liberty Tribune (Box 89, Folder 1-2)
  - Copyright Information (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - D.A.R.-Grave Marking (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - D.A.R.-Programs and Lineage Research (Box 89, Folder 5-7)
  - D.A.R.-Col. Thomas Hughart Chapter (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - D.A.R. Yearbook (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Dunlap, Boutwell-Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Family Associations (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Family Bible Records (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Forbes, Amanda (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Fort Defiance (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Guardian Bond Book, Augusta County, Virginia - November 1775-February 1804 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Guardian Bond Book II, Augusta County, Virginia - December 1804-February 1809 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Guardian Bond Book III, Augusta County, Virginia - March 1809-October 1816 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Guardian Bond Book IV, Augusta County, Virginia - 23 December 1816-24 January 1825 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Guardian Bond Book V, Augusta County, Virginia - 28 February 1825-24 June 1833 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Guardian Bond Book VI, Augusta County, Virginia - 22 July 1833-22 March 1841 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Guardian Bond Book VII, Augusta County, Virginia - 26 April 1841-26 February 1844 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Guardian Bond Book VIII, Augusta County, Virginia - 25 March 1844-25 June 1850 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Guardian Bonds, Will Book 1, 1806-1820, City of Staunton (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Hemp Certificates (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Historical Markers - Speech (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Joyner, Peggy (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Kemper Mss. (transcription) (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Kentucky Ancestors (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Legislators - Staunton and Augusta County (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Maps (Box 90, Folder 18-19)
  - Marriage Bond Indexes, 1785-1789, 1829-1844 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Index to Marriages, 1887-1910 (Augusta County) (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - "Record of Marriages of Colored Persons Returned by R. Waldo, Agent, Freedman's Bureau, December 23, 1868" (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Mexican War (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 91, Folder 3-6)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 91, Folder 7-8)
  - Mount Memorial Cemetery, Liberty, Missouri - Tombstone Inscriptions - Compiled by Frank W. Littleford (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Mount Sidney (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Mozart Hotel (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - "The New York Dress Shop" (1975) (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Notebook (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Old Homes of Augusta County (Box 91, Folder 14-15)
  - Orange Co. Will Book, 1740-1756 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Peaked Mountain and Cook's Creek Presbyterian Churches Session Book (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Pleasant Grove Church and Cemetery (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Index to Pensioners & Declarants for U.S. Government Pensions Recorded in Augusta County, Virginia, 1786-1854 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Records Restoration (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Series on Towns and Villages of Augusta Co. (Box 92, Folder 6-7)
  - History of Smithville, Missouri - Newspaper Articles by Cosby Shafer and Robert L. Patterson (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Townsend Book Bindery (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - West Augusta District - References in Augusta County, Virginia Records (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Weyers Cave (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - William & Mary Quarterly Extracts (Box 92, Folder 12-13)
  - Wisconsin Historical Society (Box 92, Folder 14)
- Compilations (Box-folder Box 92, Folder 15 - Box 96)
  - Aull-Meteer and Allied Families of Ireland, Virginia and Missouri by Edward Aull, Jr. (1965) (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - "Augusta County, Virginia Court of Claims, 1782-1785" (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - "Augusta County, Virginia - Index - Black Marriages, 1865-1910" (A-L) (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - "Augusta County, Virginia - Index - Black Marriages, 1865-1910" (M-Z) (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - The Baylor-McChesney and Related Families by Robert McChesney Bethea (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - History of the Beeton Family of Virginia by Robert D. Beeton (1979) (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - The Black Family of Augusta County, Va. and Wood County, W. Va. (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Squire Boone in Indiana by Arville L. Funk (1974) (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - "The Bourlands of Augusta and Bath Counties, Virginia" by Bernard M. Caperton (May, 1983) (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - "Historical Sketch of the Bright Family" by A.G. Green (1900) (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Some Chapman, Jolly, Rayburn and Smith Families in W. Va. & Ohio Violette S. Machir (1965) (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Records of the Families of Gilbert Christian and Moses Fisk by H.C. Christian (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - "The Ancestry of Samuel Clemens, grandfather of Mark Twain" by Raymond Martin Bell (1980) (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Charles Clendenin: His Ancestors and Some Descendants, 1826-1984 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - "Coalter Street and Beyond" by McKelden Smith (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Confederate Soldiers Buried in Augusta County,Virginia and those Buried in New Providence Presbyterian Cemetery in Rockbridge County, Va. - Compiled by Donna Huffer and Ken Purdy (1995) (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - The Crawford and Bratton Families as Related to the Hogshead/Hogsett Families of Virginia - Compiled by Jean Thomson Gillett (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - "Early Day Newspapers of Staunton, Virginia: 1790-1870" (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - The Ensminger Family of Pennsylvania by Raymond M. Bell (rev. 1977) (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - The Ensmingers of Alsace and Pennsylvania by Raymond M. Bell (1980) (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - The Fulkerson Story (Compiled by John F. Preston, 1961) (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - German Church Records - Virginia - Augusta County - St. John's Reformed (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Descendants of Frederick Hanger, 1726-1799 by Meade Hanger (1995) (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Descendants of Peter Hanger, 1726-1802 by Meade Hanger (1997) (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Harris of Albemarle and Augusta Counties, Virginia with related families - Compiled by Katherine G. Bushman (1968) (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Ancestry and Descendants of Lieut. John Henderson of Greenbrier County, Virginia, 1650-1900 by Joseph Lyon Miller, M.D. (1902) (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - The Genealogical Record of the Hogshead Family of America - Compiled by Mary Hakes Jones (1951) (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Karr Family Record: Descendants of Captain John Karr, Revolutionary Soldier, Book I, 1759-1977 by Nola M. Karr (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - A Historical Sketch of Michael Keinadt and Margaret Diller (1893) (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - "History of the Descendants of Frederick and Barbara Bailor Keller" - Compiled by Lillian Keller Peters (1990) (Box 94, Folder 7-8)
  - Descendants of Adam Kern, 1731-1975 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - "McCues of the Old Dominion" (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - A History of Monroe County, West Virginia (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - 1797 Assessment List for Pendleton County, Virginia, now West Virginia - Compiled by Amanda Arbogast Forbes (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - A History of Pendleton County, W. Va. (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Memoir of John Howe Peyton (Box 95, Folder N/A)
  - "John Rankin (1793-1886) - Abolitionist - Brown County, Ohio" - Compiled by Lloyd R. Rankin, Jr. (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - "Richard Rankin (1720-1788) - Augusta County, Virginia" - Compiled by Lloyd R. Rankin, Jr. (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - "A Register of Soldiers of the American Revolution Who Died and Lie Buried in Augusta County, Virginia" - 1986 (Box 95, Folder 3-7)
  - "Revolutionary Soldiers - Rockingham County, Virginia" (1976) (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - A History of Shenandoah County, Virginia by John W. Wayland (1927) (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - "History of James Skaggs, Sr. and Wife Rachel" by Carol Wyman Skaggs (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - St. John's German Reformed Church Register, 1765-1871, Middlebrook, Augusta County, Virginia (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - "Taylor Family of Greenbrier County" (Box 96, Folder 1-3)
  - "Valley Folk: Some Records and Reminiscenses" - Collected by Mary deCamp Banks Moore (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Genealogy of the Descendants of John Walker by Emma Siggins White (1902) (Box 96, Folder 5-8)
  - "Wallace-Wallis-Wallice Connections," Vols.1-2, (Fall, 1988- Spring 1990) (Box 96, Folder 9-10)
- Oversize Genealogical Charts
  - Hildebrand Family Genealogical Chart
  - Genealogical Tree of the Polk Family
- Oversize Maps